[upbeat hip-hop music plays]
♪ ♪
[Diamond]
Previously onForce...
-[Tommy] Who the fuck are you?
-I'm her grandson.
Who the fuck are you?
[Tommy] I'm her
fucking grandson.
How can I help you?
Give me a double shot
of Jameson.
[apprehensive music plays]
[grunts]
Well, this might
have some blowback.
Any of that gonna fall on you?
[Gloria] Not a drop.
[Rojas] We let 'em get
real comfortable outside.
Then we make
the motherfuckin' call.
[person] We'll get 'em, Rojas.
-[Jenard] Big bro!
-Baby bro.
[Jenard] Oh, my God, look
at this free man right here.
This is where Chicago Brothers
Incorporated came from.
We were the last to hold out,
thanks to you.
Which is why I'm so confused
to why you're dealing
with the yardies.
Come on, bro,
why we back on this bullshit?
[person] A'ight, this crazy
white boy
came through with Vic Flynn,
and straight Bin Ladened
-the whole shit, bro.
-[gunshots]
Who the fuck are you?
I'm the motherfucker that
just saved both of your lives.
He's fucking dead.
Getting caught up
in some low-rent shit
while the feds
are sniffing around
is not a good look for us.
-I get that.
-[Claudia] Do you?
Because making shit deals
is not the way to move forward.
Vic's not cut out
for this kind of work, Da.
What Victor does
is not women's work.
Victor runs the streets.
You keep us legit
and you look after me.
[Claudia]
I've had enough of men
telling me what to do
for one lifetime.
You know who I am?
Do you have more?
Look, I got a plan.
It's about you and me.
Just tell me I'm not too late.
I can't tell you that, Vic.
I can't.
Walter Flynn.
You have made quite the impact
on my family and my city.
But your time here in Chicago
has come to an end.
You gotta get the fuck
outta my city, son.
I don't work
for nobody no more.
Think I'm gonna stay here,
build my own shit.
I'm my own boss now.
[engine turning over]
[smooth hip-hop music plays]
[singer]
♪ Tougher than a Teflon ♪
♪ All that dope
I stepped on ♪
♪ We'll get the rest gone ♪
♪ Been that nigga
What else you want? ♪
♪ If you want
Power, powder, respect ♪
♪ Mm, mm ♪
♪ I want that money
And power and powder ♪
♪ Money and powder and power ♪
[50 Cent] ♪ That paper
That paper, paper ♪
♪ Yeah, I gotta stack that ♪
♪ Them diamonds keep blinkin'
Blinkin' ♪
♪ We might have
To check that ♪
♪ Now boy when
That blicky blicky ♪
♪ Come out
You get clapped fast ♪
♪ Draw down
With a little joint ♪
♪ I match you like pat, pat ♪
♪ Come back
When them cameras out ♪
♪ Run your block
We kick that ♪
♪ Come back when your funeral
In progress ♪
♪ Hit your back , the back ♪
♪ Your bitch ass
Won't even hit back ♪
♪ You'll be splashin'
In fashion ♪
♪ Nigga you can take
The drip ♪
♪ Catch you slippin'
We slidin' ♪
♪ You niggas
On some different shit ♪
♪ We hit the licks
We with the shit ♪
♪ Shh when you get hit ♪
♪ Quiet down ♪
♪ No need for the talkin' ♪
♪ The fuck is that about? ♪
[singer]
♪ Tougher than a Teflon ♪
♪ All the dope
I stepped on ♪
♪ Rio get the rest gone ♪
♪ Been that nigga
What else you want? ♪
♪ If you want
Power, powder, respect ♪
♪ Mm, mm ♪
♪ I want that money
And power and powder ♪
♪ Money and powder and power ♪
[pensive music playing]
[Sam Tinnesz's
"Even If It Hurts" plays]
♪ ♪
[Sam] ♪ You blink once
Then it's gone ♪
♪ Don't let it take the skin
From your bones ♪
♪ It's darkest
Before the dawn ♪
♪ But you don't need
To do this alone ♪
♪ No, you don't ♪
♪ 'Cause when you get
This close ♪
♪ You can feel the heat ♪
♪ Now you're so afraid ♪
♪ Of what's underneath ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ Don't ♪
♪ Even if it hurts ♪
♪ Even if it makes me bleed ♪
♪ I'm gonna carry you ♪
♪ Pushing through ♪
♪ With the dirt
On my sleeves ♪
♪ Even if it hurts ♪
♪ Even if it's razor deep ♪
♪ I'm not giving up ♪
♪ Not gonna run ♪
♪ I'll be there
When you need me ♪
♪ Even if it hurts ♪
Yeah.
The fuck?
[Sam] ♪ Not giving up on you ♪
♪ ♪
Hey, you ain't got
no other numbers in your phone?
Yours was the first number
I went to.
Whoever you got
on the payroll for protection,
they ain't worth shit.
Hmm, not in the budget
this month.
Is this a front?
Are you dealing out of here?
That's your takeaway
from broken windows?
[Tommy] Well, that shit
ain't too hard
to connect the dots on.
Your place gets lit up,
you don't pay for protection,
you don't call family--
You are family.
Pace yourself--
I don't know that you wanna
run into that
burning building just yet.
[JP] Look, I don't have
anybody to call.
Me and my pops own this spot.
He's been sick for a minute.
Medical bills
are cleaning me out.
At some point, it's gonna be
one or the other.
And my ex-husband
won't take my calls anymore
about this money pit
or anything else
for that matter.
You got a problem with that?
Nope, a ex is a ex.
God damn, man.
It's the third fucking time
this year the club's been hit.
Somebody trying
to get your attention.
Here, it's 10K.
Fix your windows.
Maybe get some new sheetrock.
Yeah, I appreciate the gesture,
but it won't make a dent.
[Tommy] Listen to me.
Take this money.
The way I see it,
we both alone.
[pensive music plays]
♪ ♪
[JP] Thanks.
That'll get me by
for a little while.
I got a way.
What do you mean you got a way?
A way to what?
I got a way for money
to make money.
I'll hit you later.
[percussive electronic
music plays]
♪ ♪
[singer] ♪ Hey ♪
[person on answering machine]
Mr. Flynn, this is Dr. Rudin
at River North Oncology.
We need to have a conversation
about your test results,
and we should do it
as soon as possible.
I'd like to arrange
some additional lab work.
-So please call my office to--
-[line beeps]
[coughing]
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Jesus Christ. You okay?
-I'm fine.
-Bullshit. You need a doctor.
[Flynn] I don't need nothing.
I just stood up too fast,
that's all.
-[liquor pouring]
-How bad is it?
It's nothing.
Look, we can get ahead of it,
not like with Mom.
We need to tell Claudia.
-Do not.
-She needs to know.
Claudia cannot know.
No one can know.
Are we clear?
Are we fucking clear?
Yes.
And when I'm gone, you'll lead.
Dad--
[Flynn] You need to step up,
Victor.
This is your legacy, son,
your birthright as a Flynn,
what you've been waiting for
your entire life.
And once I do go,
I'll pass the mantle to you,
and you'll make me proud.
You can count on me.
I'll make it mine.
Thing is, boy,
it doesn't quite work that way.
You see, I built this
organization out of nothing.
So you continue
to do it my way,
'cause that's how I like it,
and that's the way
Ireland wants it.
Now, if you cross them, well...
the consequences
will be fucking fatal.
[tense music plays]
♪ ♪
Hey, I want you to meet
these little motherfuckers
over here, bro--
they wild as hell,
and they some
stone-cold killers, too, G.
Don't bring them
anywhere near me.
They bad for business.
Ain't got no upside.
Okay, okay,
look, bro, I hear you,
but a lot of shit
has changed in 15 years.
You just not up on it, D.
I've been all right.
[Jenard]
Yeah, while you was inside.
But out here, shit move
at a different speed, bro,
I'm telling you.
-Listen to me--
-No, nigga, listen to me!
These little niggas
is an investment.
Period, a'ight?
They pay dividends
like a motherfucker, too.
[Diamond] They dead money.
They ain't got no shelf life.
They pull a trigger one time,
and 13 people die.
That spray-and-pray bullshit
is a bad look,
no matter how long
I been inside.
-Think.
-I hear you.
How's that help us?
[tense music plays]
♪ ♪
Who the fuck
told you I was here?
♪ ♪
Damn.
Wait a minute. I know you.
Of course you do, pendejo!
You're here to fucking kill me.
It seems like more
like you trying to kill me.
It's self-defense.
That fucking scar.
Liliana, I should have
killed you back in New York.
[siren whoops]
You dumb enough to do this
in front of an audience?
[chuckles]
I got the drop on you once.
I'll do it again.
Not a fucking chance.
Ah, fuck.
This is why
we can't have nice things.
[sentimental guitar music
plays]
♪ ♪
[singer] ♪ I know
That you're afraid ♪
♪ To take chances ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Scared of consequences ♪
♪ Of your actions ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Of who you are ♪
Vic...
-what are you doing here?
-I needed to see you.
Why? We can't keep doing this.
I can't keep doing this.
[solemn music plays]
♪ ♪
Is there someone else?
No.
When my father's gone,
I'll be free, Glo.
You're never gonna
be free, Vic.
And the fucked-up part is,
your loyalty is the reason
I love you.
Okay, so then
why can't we just--
But it's also the thing that's
gonna keep you in this
after he's gone.
Gloria--
Vic, you know you
gotta marry an Irish woman.
Have a pure white Irish son
to continue
your father's legacy.
I don't fit in that plan.
So we run away.
Baby, wherever we go,
they'll find us.
Key.
-I'm keeping my key.
-[Gloria] Victor--
If you don't want me back
in here, change the locks.
Fuck.
Yo, yo. Whoa, you lost?
How much time you got
for that answer?
Yo, what's up, man?
[Diamond] So this the white boy
you told me about?
[Jenard] Mm-hmm.
I got you, I got you.
Right here. Go ahead.
Safety's on.
Who you work for?
Nobody. I ain't got no ties.
A man alone don't last long
in these streets.
[Tommy]
Ooh, that's some deep shit.
This is you with the belt?
You was a boxer?
You a champ?
You was nice with these?
So what you got in the bag?
It's...
nothing worth dying over.
Slowly.
All right.
Why didn't you keep it?
I didn't know where you were.
I ain't in this game to snatch
chains and pick pockets.
You're a fucking idiot, bro.
I'd have
at least kept the money.
Yeah, well, we different.
Anyways, them drugs is
stepped on with baby aspirin.
So you have fun with that.
We done and done?
Hmm.
-Ah-ah-ah-ah-ah.
-Today ain't the day.
-It's always the day, boy.
-That right?
You trying
to try something, huh?
Yeah, why not? Why don't you
take this, motherfucker?
Yo, I didn't come here
to set shit off,
I came here to make shit right.
-[door closes]
-Elijah, you a fool.
Now, put them goddamn guns
down in my shop.
[tense music plays]
Now!
Nigga, I ain't doing shit
'tl I get the fucking nod.
What the fuck you
looking at him for?
-This my spot.
-[person] Hey, man, fuck that.
Hey, J, who calling
the shots here?
Give me the word,
I smoke white boy right now.
Fuck it. Put it down.
We gonna let him make it.
My little niggas.
♪ ♪
Take care of that.
Let's walk.
All right.
-Fuck.
-[door closes]
I heard you did
the same thing for Flynn.
Why the fuck are you out here
trying to make friends?
I ain't trying to make friends.
I'm out here trying
to make money and moves.
[person]
Don't you fucking move!
-I'm guessing this your ride?
-[Diamond] Fuck, no.
[person]
Don't you fucking move!
Keep your fucking hands
where I can see 'em. Back up!
Jefe'sgot a job
for you, Diamond.
[Tommy] Do these motherfuckers
know you?
[person] Rojas knows you.
I guess that answers that.
-[person] Let's go. Come on.
-Get the fuck in the car.
[person] Move it, skillet!
♪ ♪
Don't fucking move.
I swear to God I'll blow
your fucking head off.
Llévatelo!
You thought you was gonna
put our jefe
in a wheelchair
and life was just gonna
go on like that shit
didn't happen, huh?
[chuckles]
I knew you would come for me,
but he's not a part it.
He's seen our faces.
He's a big fucking part of it.
Yeah, well, you the one
who took the bags
off our heads, mamacita.
That's, like, kidnapping 101.
Excuse me, motherfucker?
Now I'm part of it.
You fucker.
[gun cocks]
[Diamond] Stop.
If you want me, here I am.
[grunts]
¿Sabes qué?
This is all on you.
Rojas wants you
moving our shit today.
-I don't move H.
-Today you do!
In fact, you're gonna move
all eight bricks of it for us.
The city is on fire with cops.
Which is why you're
gonna do it and we're not.
Either you bring us our money,
or you die
in the fucking street.
[person] This is what you get
for fucking up Rojas,
puto, ¿claro?
[person 2]
He stays behind as collateral.
If you want this done
while the city
is crawling with heat,
then I'm gonna need
a wheelman.
He's my guy.
I walked in with him.
I'm not
walking out without him.
[person 2]
You're dead either way.
[speaks Spanish]
Don't make a promise
you can keep.
[person 2] If you don't bring
us the money in three hours,
you'll be dead,
motherfucker.
Oh.
[device beeps]
-[Vic] How's the count, Claud?
-[Claudia] Good to the number.
I saw Peggy Shaughnessy
at the gym the other day.
-Don't start with that.
-I'm just saying--
You're saying
the same shit he is.
Look, I think Gloria's great.
But you and I both know Dad's
never gonna go for that.
The fuck am I supposed
to do about it?
Find your happiness, Vic.
[chuckles]
Shit's easy for you.
Are you fucking kidding me?
Nothing about Da
and me is easy.
You know, you've got
the brass fucking ring,
and you don't even fuck--
I'm not doing this shit.
You've got your shit,
and I've got mine.
-Fair?
-Whatever.
Look, I think I found
the next big bounce in Chicago.
Chemical solution to make up
for all our lost business.
Pop will never go
for that designer shit.
-We're not trying to expand.
-We need to expand.
-Let me talk to him about it.
-It won't make a difference.
Okay, so then
he'll listen to you.
Can you put that
garbage away, please?
[sirens wailing]
God damn.
You wasn't joking
about that heat.
There's been 37 shootings
in the last weekend.
Hotter than a motherfucker.
We gonna get this done.
I ain't even been
in this city long enough
to have any enemies.
You just opened up the face
of one of Rojas' homies.
You right.
I got one enemy.
Wait, two.
Ah, shit. I-I got three.
Three enemies.
That's definitely it.
So what's Rojas' crew's beef
with you, anyways?
You put some dude in a chair?
Why you didn't put him
in the ground?
Wasn't trying to get life
while I was inside.
That shit all happened fast.
Rojas tried to get at Jenard,
take some CBI business.
I put a end to that.
Been taking care of Jenard
his whole life.
Now that you out,
he been the man.
Holding everything
down for you.
Taking care
of your whole organization.
Calling the shots.
Holding down the hood.
How's that going for you?
[tense music playing]
♪ ♪
Look, I know
you ain't no fucking cop.
So what's your angle?
Stack as much paper
in this city as I can.
How much you looking to make?
I ain't got no limit.
Look, you got my ass
out a jam.
I'm doing the same for you.
Break me off whatever.
And at the end of this,
you go your way, I go mine's.
Deal?
Done.
[Rojas] There's too much heat
on the streets
to risk our men.
So Diamond better
get this shit done fast.
The cartel
needs the money tonight,
or heads will start rolling.
I've got Diamond's brother.
Let's make this shit
real interesting for him.
♪ ♪
Yo, you gotta be stealth
as a motherfucker
right now, D.
Everything's quiet once you
get north of Fullerton fully.
Good looking, E.
Jenard show up yet?
[Elijah]
Nah, he ain't picking up.
Shit don't feel right.
Let me know when he lands.
♪ ♪
-Five-O.
-[Tommy] All right, be cool.
We ain't doing nothing wrong.
I'm a Black man with two
fucking cop cars behind me.
[Tommy] Hope the cops are
more chill here in Chicago
than they are in New York.
I'm sure they flex
just as hard.
DWB is coast to coast.
-[siren chirps]
-Fuck, they just lit us up.
-[sighs]
-You all right.
Keep your foot on the brake.
We all right, we all right.
-I just got out.
-[sirens wailing]
-[Tommy] We all right.
-[wailing continues]
[Diamond] We clear.
[laughs] God damn!
[sighs]
♪ ♪
Yo, people gonna know
fast these keys are dropping.
Word up. Circle the block once.
-If I ain't out--
-Take off. Got it.
No, motherfucker,
circle a second time.
Just fucking wit you.
I'll have eyes on you
the whole time.
[tense music playing]
♪ ♪
[machinery whirring]
[speaking Spanish]
My hablois bad.
-[speaks Spanish]
-I came in clean.
Oh, I know exactly
what that mean.
-Who the fuck sent you here?
-Rojas.
-Really?
-Yeah.
I don't see nothing
in your hand.
Well, I didn't know what
was waiting for me in here.
-Where's my package?
-It's outside.
Them three dumpsters?
Underneath the second one.
What else is waiting
for me out there?
Nothing. Seriously.
Look, if I'm lying to you,
y'all could cut me up next.
Right.
♪ ♪
I got a '69 Mustang.
Nobody cares.
My Spanish is getting better.
Pay me.
You working strictly for Rojas?
Not even. I'm a free agent.
Where do I find you?
Don't worry about it.
I'll find you first, tía.
[upbeat hip-hop music plays]
-[singer] ♪ I'm in ♪
-[singer] ♪ Go, go ♪
Maybe we the junkies, huh?
Not me. I never touch it.
No, I mean, you know,
chasing that first high
when we got away with it.
Had some paper
for the first time,
-some power...
-Yeah. Yeah.
I can tell you
every detail the time
I climbed the steps at Cabrini.
Dime bag of ditch weed
in my pocket...
...ready to make my first deal.
Yo, man, I was slinging
that same shit.
One-thirty-four
and Guy R Brewer.
Just happy to be in the mix.
Make that ten dollars.
See, Jenard,
he don't understand
how things used to be.
He thinks things just
supposed to jump off
-at the speed of light.
-Nah, nah, nah.
We had to do it
slow and steady.
Right. We saw the angles.
[phone buzzing]
[person] Change of plans.
Cops are moving heavy,
and we want our fucking money!
[person 2]
You have an hour to finish
all the drops,
or baby brother dies.
-Fuck.
-[Tommy] We got to hurry.
[engine revving]
We gotta make these drops.
Come on, you know Rojas
ain't dealing no trash.
I know him. I don't know you.
[tense music plays]
♪ ♪
[Diamond]
Come on.
Where are you?
♪ ♪
Fuck it.
It's very high level.
It's the best.
So we got a deal?
Last test.
♪ ♪
[door chimes, beeps]
[Diamond] Shalom, brother.
What can I get you?
[smacks counter]
Let me get
some of that pastrami.
Two pounds, lean.
♪ ♪
Need anything else?
Um, yeah, yeah.
Let me get some
of these cinnamon cookies.
It's rugelach.
Yeah, whatever they are,
they damn good.
Isaak. Money.
It's all there.
Get the fuck out of here.
You know what?
That's good. That's enough.
-[doorbell chimes, beeps]
-Shalom, brother.
[Walter] How's your count?
Perfect.
Best bookkeeper I ever had.
What would I do without you?
[Claudia] Who knows?
We got Lincoln Park
due for a re-up.
[Walter] Oh, yeah?
Da, what we're selling
is outdated.
It's not fucking outdated.
It's dependable.
There are newer drugs
out there.
We need something exclusive.
Every couple of years,
some dealer comes along
with some fucking drug
that never amounts to shite.
That's not what
I'm talking about.
Dad, we're losing money.
Why the fuck do you insist
on pushing your way into a room
where you're not wanted?
Just run the fucking books
and the legitimate floats.
That's it.
He runs the fucking streets,
all right?
Now, is there
any other business
concerning the count
that we need to discuss?
No, nothing.
♪ ♪
Arnaud?
-Arnaud?
-You got the drop?
[Tommy] Yeah, I do.
Where you want it?
-[sniffs]
-Test it, don't bump it.
What the fuck are you doing?
Just pay me my money,
motherfucker.
I gotta get going.
I ain't got time for this shit.
Yo, yo, money.
-You nodding out on me?
-[body thuds]
You fucking mutt.
Where's the money at?
Here we go.
One, two, three.
[siren whooping]
[officer]
Driver...
roll down your window.
Hey, slowly.
I saw you on your cell phone.
You know, it's illegal
to text and drive.
-The car was parked, Officer.
-License and registration.
I'd rather not make
any movements, sir.
Prefer to keep my hands
where you can see 'em
at all times
in fear that
they may be perceived
as a threat against you.
[officer]
You are operating a vehicle
with out-of-state plates.
I'm not gonna ask you again.
Slowly retrieve your license
from your wallet
and the registration
from the glove box, now.
I will not move my hands
from the steering wheel, sir.
Driver, license
from your wallet
and registration
from that glove box, now!
-[gun cocks]
-This is not my vehicle, sir.
Are you currently
operating a vehicle
that you are not the owner of?
Driver, step out
of this fucking car now.
Do not make me ask you again!
Sir, I will not reach
for that door.
I will not make
any sudden movements.
My hands are staying
on this steering wheel.
[Tommy]
Is there a problem, Officer?
Is there a problem with my car?
I know the tags are current,
I'm not in a red zone.
I don't see any meters.
[indistinct chatter
over police radio]
-This is your car, bro?
-Yeah, she sure is.
Do you know this man?
I sure do.
It's David Samson, my barber.
Anything else
I can help you with?
Give me your license
and registration.
No prob.
I swear to God,
I was inside for ten minutes.
It was s-sunny,
and now it's snowing.
[officer] Yeah, welcome
to Chicago, bro.
Another ten minutes,
we'll be going to a barbecue.
[laughs]
[softly] Not if your life
depended on it, cocksucker.
Stay cool.
[car door closes]
License, registration.
Um, give me a minute
to run these.
Yeah, yeah, of course.
Holy shit.
What is he gonna find
running your plates?
He ain't gonna find nothing.
Not even a parking ticket?
Nothing.
[car door closes]
-Long way from the Big Apple.
-[Tommy] Yeah.
I heard good things
about your pizza.
All lies.
[chuckles]
Hey, you two have a good day.
You too, bro.
-[car door closes]
-Fifteen fucking years inside,
and this is the one thing that
ain't change a goddamn bit.
[Tommy]
Let's go get your brother.
[tense music plays]
♪ ♪
[Diamond] Where's my brother?
Where's
my motherfucking brother?
[Tommy]
Yo, we did all the drops.
You got your money.
[person] Don't fucking move.
You move, you die.
[person 2] And every dollar
better be in there.
I'm not playing.
Slow the fuck down. Slow down.
The money.
Hmm?
♪ ♪
Yo, J, you good?
I'm good.
Ooh-hoo-hoo-hoo.
[chuckles] I like.
♪ ♪
Come on.
Let's go!
Just throw them the fuck down.
Go.
[Diamond] Go, go, go, go.
♪ ♪
[Elijah]
A quarter, big bro.
Twenty-five for a day's work.
Like I said, whatever's good.
[siren wailing in the distance]
How'd you know
my name is David?
Nobody's called me that
for 30 years.
I see shit
where nobody else look.
You not that deep, bro.
You saw it
on my barber's license, huh?
Mm-hmm.
So why'd you take the ride?
Backup.
[Diamond] No. [chuckles]
You not the backup
kind of motherfucker.
I saw your head was
on a swivel at every drop.
You absorbed everything
about the routes.
You clocking my city?
It gonna be a problem if I am?
Only one way to find out.
Let's find out, then.
Hmm.
Watch your back.
Hello?
[JP] Hey, what's up?
Welcome to Grandma's house.
[Tommy] Jesus.[chuckles]
[JP] Anything look familiar?
Not really.
I guess I kind of remember
this couch, though.
[JP] Sweating outside
in the summer
and then getting stuck to it
as soon as you sat down.
-Yeah. Yeah, your thighs.
-Yeah.
When you came off it,
it sounded like Fruit Roll-Ups.
-Like Velcro Fruit Roll-Ups.
-[both laugh]
Uh, yo, man, you want a beer?
Yeah.
[bottles clink]
-Here you go.
-Here, I'll trade you.
[JP] The fuck?
[Tommy]
I told you I had a way.
Take it for, uh, the club,
you know, for damages
or for your divorce
or whatever.
-Take it. Go ahead.
-Uh, Tommy, uh...
Hold up, man.
Look what I found.
I finally know who this is.
Get ready for the show.
Check this shit out.
What's this?
[sentimental music plays]
No fucking way.
[chuckles]
Okay, let's go play.
Come on, it'll be fun.
♪ ♪
Wow.
[laughs] Hey.
Let me get that off there.
♪ ♪
[JP] I can't believe she left
her own fucking child.
I would never do that.
How you know what you would do?
Because I fucking love my son.
Fought as hard as
I could to hold on to him.
How old is he?
Sixteen last July, but, um...
I haven't seen him in 14 years.
When I came out,
his mother took him away.
I fought hard to be a part
of his life, but, uh...
he vanished.
[tense music plays]
Being a father
was the best thing
that ever happened to me.
Now I don't know...
who he is or-or where he is.
After my son was pulled
from my life,
family was just me
and my pops.
Then all of a sudden,
you show up.
And now I...
Look, I-I don't know
how all this shit works.
I never had a brother.
I did.
[pounding]
[tense music plays]
[person] You motherfucker!
We're gonna kill you!
[pounding continues]
[person 2] When Rojas hears
about this, motherfucker!
[pounding continues]
Rojas is gonna fuck you up!
[person] Pendejo!
Hey, I can't wait
to kill you, motherfucker.
[person 2]
Fucking pussy, I swear to God!
[pounding continues]
Let us the fuck out of here,
you bitch!
This shit ain't over!
You can't do this to us!
[pounding continues]
You motherfucker!
Hell of a city.
[dark music]
♪ ♪
[person] Hey!
[upbeat hip-hop music plays]
[person 2] Let me out!
[screaming]
[Lee Richardson's "Diamond"
plays]
♪ ♪
[singer] ♪ Shining bright
In every place that I win ♪
♪ Leave a legacy
Believe it's perfect timing ♪
♪ Look up at the sky
The stars are aligning ♪
♪ Yeah
They tried, and they failed ♪
♪ But, no, you ain't ever
Gon' break this diamond ♪
[singers] ♪ Whoa ♪
Now you owe me one more.
Oh, fuck.
[singer] ♪ Diamond ♪
♪ No you ain't never gon' ♪
♪ No you ain't never
Gon' break this ♪
♪ No you ain't ever
♪ ♪
[singer] ♪ They tried
And they failed ♪
♪ And they tried
♪ No you ain't never gon'
Break this diamond ♪
♪ Yeah, they tried
And they failed ♪
♪ And they tried
♪ But, no, you ain't never
Gon' break this greatness ♪
This motherfucker.
♪ ♪
How'd you get
in the bar business anyway?
It's a tough racket.
Yeah, it wasn't my plan A.
Plan A was to open
a fancy Jamaican spot.
But, you know, this place
has a small kitchen
that keeps me inspired.
-To inspiration.
-[Gloria chuckles]
[reggae music playing softly
on speakers]
And it was affordable,
so I thought...
That why you kicking it up
to the Irish guys?
♪ ♪
I know a payment envelope
when I see it.
Oh, yeah?
[Tommy] Yeah.
Ain't no shame being in a jam.
I ain't ashamed.
Did what I had
to do at the time.
You want me to take
care of that for you?
Give Junior some of this,
one of those,
take them out
with the quickness?
Pah!
[laughs]
Put your damn cape away.
I ain't trying to be saved.
Got myself in.
I'll get myself out.
Cheers to that.
♪ ♪
[Gloria] Why'd you come back?
Finally found
a reason to stay.
-Don't worry. It ain't you.
-[laughs]
-I don't know, there's just...
-[distant clatter]
...something about this town.
Yeah, I feel like
I could breathe here.
Look, there's something
you should know about me.
You don't have
to tell me nothing.
No, there's someone that--
♪ ♪
There always is.
[suspenseful music plays]
♪ ♪
[Travis Scott] ♪ For this life
I cannot change ♪
♪ Hidden Hills
Deep off in the main ♪
♪ M&Ms
Sweet like candy cane ♪
♪ Drop the top ♪
♪ Pop it, let it bang ♪
♪ For this life
I cannot change ♪
♪ Hidden Hills
Deep off in the main ♪
♪ M&Ms
Sweet like candy cane ♪
♪ Drop the top ♪
♪ Pop it, let it bang ♪
♪ ♪
[person] I'm coming.
What the fuck do you want?
The game ended two hours ago.
I ain't here for no game.
I want you to move.
And I want you to forget
that I was ever here.
I don't know, Goldie.
I got a real good memory.
Motherfucker.
♪ ♪
Let me grab my toothbrush.
[Tommy] Buy a new one.
[Travis Scott] ♪ For this life
I cannot change ♪
♪ Hidden Hills
Deep off in the main ♪
♪ M&Ms
Sweet like candy cane ♪
♪ Drop the top ♪
♪ Pop it, let it bang ♪
[singer]
♪ Pop it, pop it ♪
♪ For this life
I cannot change ♪
♪ Hidden Hills
Deep off in the main ♪
♪ M&Ms
Sweet like candy cane ♪
♪ Drop the top ♪
♪ Pop it, let it bang ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ ♪
[indistinct chatter on TV]
[tense music plays]
[distant clatter]
♪ ♪
How'd you find me?
-Who else knows I'm here?
-Fuck you!
Oh, yeah, you sure?
You wanna repeat that?
[Liliana yelps]
How'd you know where I live?
[Tommy] I'm that fucking good.
♪ ♪
[Liliana coughs, wheezes]
Ain't nobody gonna help you
now, Liliana.
I got the drop on you.
So you better tell me...
how the fuck did you find me?
Divine intervention.
You fucking bitch.
No, no, I'm-I'm
fucking serious, all right?
After Julio gave me money
to leave New York,
I ended up here, and I-I was
having a good fucking life
until I started hearing about
some white boy, new in town,
blue fucking Mustang.
Are they the ones
who helped you find me?
No, all right?
You're a complete mystery
to them.
They don't know shit about you.
-You lie!
-[Liliana screams]
[Liliana]
I didn't track you, Tommy.
I figured you were here
to finish me.
So I came at you first.
Every time Ghost
left somebody alive
out of his generosity,
it came to bite us in the ass.
Motherfucker.
♪ ♪
It's always good
running into old friends.
[singer] ♪ I'll have
The common decency ♪
♪ To piece you apart
I know you taste defeat ♪
♪ Makin' 'em beat
From the start ♪
♪ You know this shit
Isn't a fight ♪
♪ If you ain't leavin'
We'll march ♪
♪ Nothing I do's in vain ♪
♪ Besides I ain't new
To the game ♪
♪ I'm who's to blame for
Taking all this punishment ♪
♪ 'Cause I learn to fight
Through the pain ♪
♪ I'm wiping off my blood
Off my wounds ♪
♪ Bitch, I can
Keep scrapping ♪
♪ Deep passion
Making you snap ♪
♪ But keep your feet tapping ♪
♪ You don't know
The half of it ♪
♪ I've been gone
For a minute ♪
♪ But I ain't finished ♪
♪ I'm right back
On my savage shit ♪
♪ You thought this shit
Would be smooth ♪
♪ But I ain't having it ♪
♪ I lay 'em out
Like the money ♪
♪ Under the mattresses ♪
♪ I'm too ill, aim to kill ♪
♪ All of my oppositions
Mind's made ♪
♪ Ain't no deals, our fucking
Proposition's cutthroat ♪
♪ They want smoke
Tell 'em to come with it ♪
♪ I'ma show 'em exactly just
Who they fucking with ♪
♪ I'm back, motherfuckers
Guess who's back ♪
♪ I said I'm back
Motherfuckers ♪
♪ Guess who's back ♪
♪ And I was gone
But I'm back, motherfuckers ♪
♪ I'm right here ♪
♪ Welcome home 'cause
I'm back, motherfuckers ♪
♪ This nigga back ♪
♪ Thought it was smooth
But I'm back, motherfuckers ♪
♪ I ain't leaving ♪
♪ I'm in my groove 'cause
I'm back, motherfuckers ♪
♪ Where we going? ♪
♪ Now I'm really about
To snap, motherfucker ♪
♪ About to snap ♪
♪ 'Cause they know a nigga
Back, motherfucker ♪
♪ Yeah, I'm back ♪
♪ Yeah, I'm back
Motherfucker ♪
♪ ♪